const programmingJokes = [
    { id: 0, question: "Why don't programmers like nature?", answer: "It has too many bugs." },
    { id: 1, question: "Why did the CSS developer go to therapy?", answer: "To get rid of his margins." },
    { id: 2, question: "How do you comfort a JavaScript developer?", answer: " You console them." },
    { id: 3, question: "Why did the CSS developer leave the restaurant?", answer: "Because it had no class." },
    { id: 4, question: "Why did the JavaScript developer go missing?", answer: "Because he didn't know when to return." },
    { id: 5, question: "Why did the HTML tag go to the party?", answer: "Because it wanted to break the line." },
    { id: 6, question: "Why do JavaScript developers wear glasses?", answer: "Because they don't C#." },
    { id: 7, question: "Why don't programmers like to use inline styles?", answer: "Because they want to be classy." },
    { id: 8, question: "Why did the CSS selector break up with the HTML element?", answer: "It found someone more specific." },
    { id: 9, question: "Why did the CSS developer apply for a job?", answer: "They wanted to get a position." },
];

function getRandomInt(max) {
    return Math.floor(Math.random() * max);
}

const joke = getRandomInt(programmingJokes.length)

console.log("######################")
console.log("Hello, I'm one Joke machine!")
console.log()
console.log("Joke #" + programmingJokes[joke].id)
console.log("Question: " + programmingJokes[joke].question)
console.log("Answer: " + programmingJokes[joke].answer)
console.log()
